M LALLY

BERLIN/REMOTE // LALLYM@PM.ME // +4915778414713

ABOUT LALLY

I am an enthusiastic self-starter, driven through personal accomplishments, and a desire to learn. I am searching for a dynamic and exciting working environment aligned with my values of diversity and inclusion, where I can contribute to a positive experience not only for users, but for all people affected by the decisions and choices I make.

EDUCATION

- 2023/24 Advanced UI @ Cimdata
 Multiple modules to expand existing UI skills
- 2021/22 UX Bootcamp @ CareerFoundry Thorough course covering entire UX process
- 2020 Udacity User Experience Nanodegree Online program covering all stages of UX design
- 2014 Aviation Finance Finuas Network Intensive training course on Aircraft leasing
- 2010-14 B.A. Psychology & Sociology @UL
 2:1 Honours degree at the University of Limerick
- 2004/10 Sacred Heart School High school, studying History, Spanish, Art, Biology

VOLUNTEERING

- Tubman Network Refugee assistance Driver coordination for housing incoming bipoc folks arriving from Ukraine.
- Queer.Haus nonprofit social network UX researcher & designer for various projects
- Plantage Vegan Organic Farming Veggie delivery volunteer
- YMCA Interpoint hostel, Copenhagen
 Office admin & general running of non-profit
 local YMCA Hostel

SKILLS

- Figma
- Webflow
- Scrum
- Research
- Data analysis
- Adobe suite
- Inkscape

- HTML & CSS
- E-Commerce
- Lit research
- Miro
- Salesforce
- Spanish B1
- German B2

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

-UX / UI Intern

ImpactNexus, Nov 2022 - Jan 2023

An short internship to help the company launch new functionality for the product. This was my first experience working with Scrum management. My main responsibilities included defining and refining user flows and translating to UI in Figma before development.

—SENIOR CONSULTANT / SALES PlusDental, Jun 2021 - Dec 2021

A commission based position that required a high level of knowledge of dentistry and a clear image of each patient's individual needs. My role included telesales, customer support, admin tasks and training.

—HEALTH MANAGER / SALES Qunomedical, Jan 2018 - Jun 2021

A commission based position that required a high level of knowledge of medical practices and a clear image of each patient's individual needs, as well as my own ability to track my progress. My role included telesales, customer support, treatment scheduling and content creation.

—CORPORATE BOOKINGS AGENT Blacklane, Sep 2016 - Dec 2017

A specialised position booking appointments and acting as the point of contact for the most important clients of the company. My role included customer support, scheduling, admin tasks and training.

-INFLIGHT CREW PLANNER

Ryanair, Dec 2014 - Jul 2016

A scheduling and monitoring position, that required adhering to rigorous mandated safety requirements in very high volumes. My role included crew scheduling, base communication, report building and safety checks.

PSYCHOLOGY RESEARCH ASSISTANT UL, Jan 2012 - Jul 2012

An internship in the University of Limerick psychology department, conducting quantitative research. My role included collecting, inputting and analysing data, and facilitating research groups for data collection.